(Raj:)You know what would be fun?
(Raj:)-Signing Sheldon up for online dating.
-Yeah, right.
(Raj:)No, think about it.
We make it an experiment.
(Raj:)Like when Frankenstein's monster
was lonely and he found a wife.
(Howard:)He didn't find a wife.
(Howard:)They built him a wife
out of dead body parts.
(Raj:)Okay, we'll call that plan B.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)Coming.
(Penny:)Damn you, you rat bastard.
(Leonard:)Are you drunk?
(Penny:)Zack was a perfectly nice guy
and then you ruined him.
(Leonard:)How did I ruin him?
Because in the olden days,
I never would've known he was so stupid.
(Leonard:)-Come on, he wasn't that stupid.
-Yes, he was.
(Penny:)He thought you were
gonna blow up the moon.
Okay, yeah, he's stupid. Heh, heh.